The cold wind blows and scatters your scent,
Brushing past my heart
Like a final goodbye,
Coldly sweeping through my soul
These foolish hands that tried to hold you
Now fall helplessly to my side
Though I knew that it was over,
There were days I still could not let go
Goodbye my love my everything
I won't try to hold you anymore
It's time to let you go
Now I have to set you free,
Keeping you buried deep within my heart
This aching final farewell,
I have to let you go through tears
The last say goodbye
I see a silhouette that looks like you
And force a smile, pretending I'm okay
In a faded photograph,
You're still smiling, bright as ever
Memories as vivid as yesterday
Leave me hurting once again today
Every moment that we shared
Now feels like a distant, fragile dream
Goodbye my love my everything
I won't try to hold you anymore
It's time to let you go
Now I have to set you free,
Keeping you buried deep within my heart
This aching final farewell,
I have to let you go through tears
The last say goodbye
Perhaps forgetting you
Was always an impossible thing
But now I have to face the truth —
Our story has to end right here
I tried to hold on
but I can't no more
Goodbye my love my everything
I won't try to hold you anymore
It's time to let you go
Now I have to set you free,
Keeping you buried deep within my heart
This aching final farewell,
I have to let you go through tears
The last say goodbye
Goodbye, my love…
Please be happy
Farewell my love